var arrAllQuestions = [
		objQuestion = {
			id: 0,
			question: "Who was the captain of the <em>U.S.S. Enterprise</em> prior to Kirk taking command?",
			distractor1: "Robert April",
			distractor2: "Christopher Pike",
			distractor3: "Matt Decker",
			distractor4: "Morgan Tracy",
			correctAnswer: "Christopher Pike",
			questionPic: "pike",
			questionPicAlt: "Captain Christopher Pike"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 1,
			question: "Who is the genetically engineered 'superman' the crew of the <em>U.S.S. Enterprise</em> discovered in the episode <em>Space Seed</em>?",
			distractor1: "Clark Kent",
			distractor2: "Trelane",
			distractor3: "Khan",
			distractor4: "Charlie X",
			correctAnswer: "Khan",
			questionPic: "khan",
			questionPicAlt: "KHAAAAAANNNNN!!!"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 2,
			question: "What was the name of the silicon-based life form encountered by the miners on Janus VI?",
			distractor1: "Excalibian",
			distractor2: "Melkotian",
			distractor3: "Horta",
			distractor4: "Metron",
			correctAnswer: "Horta",
			questionPic: "horta",
			questionPicAlt: "the Horta"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 3,
			question: "What is the name of the irresistible mating urge Vulcans experience every seven years?",
			distractor1: "<em>Kolinahr</em>",
			distractor2: "<em>Plak-tow</em>",
			distractor3: "<em>Pon farr</em>",
			distractor4: "<em>Fal-tor-pan</em>",
			correctAnswer: "<em>Pon farr</em>",
			questionPic: "ponfarr",
			questionPicAlt: "Spock deep in the throws of Pon Farr"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 4,
			question: "What is the name of Harry Mudd's shrewish wife?",
			distractor1: "Ruth",
			distractor2: "Janice",
			distractor3: "Stella",
			distractor4: "Edith",
			correctAnswer: "Stella",
			questionPic: "stella",
			questionPicAlt: "Harry Mudd's wife Stella"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 5,
			question: "What was the name of Spock's father?",
			distractor1: "Stonn",
			distractor2: "Sarek",
			distractor3: "T'Pau",
			distractor4: "Surak",
			correctAnswer: "Sarek",
			questionPic: "sarek",
			questionPicAlt: "Spock's father Sarek"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 6,
			question: "Who was the unscrupulous entrepreneur who sold tribbles?",
			distractor1: "Harry Mudd",
			distractor2: "Cyrano Jones",
			distractor3: "Trelane",
			distractor4: "Korax",
			correctAnswer: "Cyrano Jones",
			questionPic: "cyrano",
			questionPicAlt: "Cyrano Jones"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 7,
			question: "What was the name of the card game Kirk 'taught' the Iotians?",
			distractor1: "Kronk",
			distractor2: "Sabacc",
			distractor3: "Fizzbin",
			distractor4: "Supernova",
			correctAnswer: "Fizzbin",
			questionPic: "fizzbin",
			questionPicAlt: "the fake card game Fizzbin"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 8,
			question: "Who designed the computers on board the <em>U.S.S. Enterprise</em>?",
			distractor1: "Dr. Elizabeth Dehner",
			distractor2: "Dr. M'Benga",
			distractor3: "Dr. Richard Daystrom",
			distractor4: "Dr. Carter",
			correctAnswer: "Dr. Richard Daystrom",
			questionPic: "daystrom",
			questionPicAlt: "Dr. Richard Daystrom"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 9,
			question: "What does IDIC stand for?",
			distractor1: "Internal Deliberations end Intrusive Conflicts",
			distractor2: "Infinite Diversity in Infinite Combinations",
			distractor3: "Iterations Develop Inherent Cohesiveness",
			distractor4: "I Desire Intuitive Coherence",
			correctAnswer: "Infinite Diversity in Infinite Combinations",
			questionPic: "idic",
			questionPicAlt: "the IDIC symbol"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 10,
			question: "What race of beings had ships that could create a web of energy to trap other vessels?",
			distractor1: "Elasians",
			distractor2: "Tholians",
			distractor3: "Scalosians",
			distractor4: "Andorians",
			correctAnswer: "Tholians",
			questionPic: "tholian",
			questionPicAlt: "The Tholians trapping the Enterprise in an energy web"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 11,
			question: "Which episode featured the firsts interracial kiss on American network television?",
			distractor1: "<em>Wink of an Eye</em>",
			distractor2: "<em>Plato's Stepchildren</em>",
			distractor3: "<em>Day of the Dove</em>",
			distractor4: "<em>Elaan of Troyius</em>",
			correctAnswer: "<em>Plato's Stepchildren</em>",
			questionPic: "uhura-kirk",
			questionPicAlt: "Uhura and Kirk from Plato's Stepchildren"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 12,
			question: "What was the name of the last episode that aired of the original series?",
			distractor1: "<em>All Our Yesterdays</em>",
			distractor2: "<em>The Savage Curtain</em>",
			distractor3: "<em>Turnabout Intruder</em>",
			distractor4: "<em>The Way to Eden</em>",
			correctAnswer: "<em>Turnabout Intruder</em>",
			questionPic: "turnabout",
			questionPicAlt: "Turnabout Intruder"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 13,
			question: "More famous for playing Lurch from <em>The Addams Family</em>, whom did actor Ted Cassidy play in the episode <em>What Are Little Girls Made Of?</em>?",
			distractor1: "Dr. Carter",
			distractor2: "Dr. Korby",
			distractor3: "Ruk",
			distractor4: "Lt. Rayburn",
			correctAnswer: "Ruk",
			questionPic: "ruk",
			questionPicAlt: "Ruk"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 14,
			question: "What episode first showed Spock performing a Vulcan mind-meld?",
			distractor1: "<em>Miri</em>",
			distractor2: "<em>Conscience of the King</em>",
			distractor3: "<em>Dagger of the Mind</em>",
			distractor4: "<em>What Are Little Girls Made Of?</em>",
			correctAnswer: "<em>Dagger of the Mind</em>",
			questionPic: "mind-meld",
			questionPicAlt: "Spock performing the Vulcan Mind Meld"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 15,
			question: "Actor William Campbell portrayed both Trelane from <em>The Squire of Gothos</em> and which Klingon captain?",
			distractor1: "Kor",
			distractor2: "Koloth",
			distractor3: "Korax",
			distractor4: "Kang",
			correctAnswer: "Koloth",
			questionPic: "koloth",
			questionPicAlt: "William Campbell as Klingon Captain Koloth"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 16,
			question: "Which actress &mdash; famous for her role in the nighttime soap opera <em>Dynasty</em> &mdash; played Kirk's lover in <em>The City on the Edge of Forever</em>?",
			distractor1: "Linda Evans",
			distractor2: "Diahann Carroll",
			distractor3: "Emma Samms",
			distractor4: "Joan Collins",
			correctAnswer: "Joan Collins",
			questionPic: "keeler",
			questionPicAlt: "Joan Collins as Edith Keeler"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 17,
			question: "What legendary science fiction author wrote the episode <em>The City on the Edge of Forever</em>?",
			distractor1: "Ray Bradbury",
			distractor2: "Robert Bloch",
			distractor3: "Isaac Asimov",
			distractor4: "Harlan Ellison",
			correctAnswer: "Harlan Ellison",
			questionPic: "city",
			questionPicAlt: "City On The Edge Of Forever"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 18,
			question: "What is the most common Vulcan greeting?",
			distractor1: "'Peace be with you'",
			distractor2: "'Live long and prosper'",
			distractor3: "'We are of the body'",
			distractor4: "'Same to you, Pal.'",
			correctAnswer: "'Live long and prosper'",
			questionPic: "spock",
			questionPicAlt: "Spock giving the Vulcan salute"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 19,
			question: "Whose fatal sacrifice gives Kirk the idea of how to destroy the planet-killer in <em>The Doomsday Machine</em>?",
			distractor1: "Edith Keeler's",
			distractor2: "Matt Decker's",
			distractor3: "Yeoman Rand's",
			distractor4: "Ben Finney's",
			correctAnswer: "Matt Decker's",
			questionPic: "decker",
			questionPicAlt: "Commodore Matt Decker"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 20,
			question: "Who was the drill thrall who taught Kirk to fight on Triseklion, as he taught her to love?",
			distractor1: "Galt",
			distractor2: "Lars",
			distractor3: "Shahna",
			distractor4: "Kloog",
			correctAnswer: "Shahna",
			questionPic: "gamesters",
			questionPicAlt: "The Gamesters of Triseklion"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 21,
			question: "What is the only cure for the bite of the mugato?",
			distractor1: "Teer",
			distractor2: "Mahko root",
			distractor3: "Scalosian water",
			distractor4: "Masiform D",
			correctAnswer: "Mahko root",
			questionPic: "mugato",
			questionPicAlt: "The Mugato"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 22,
			question: "What is the name of Gary Seven's multipurpose tool that is disguised as a pen?",
			distractor1: "Sonic Screwdriver",
			distractor2: "Servo",
			distractor3: "Beta-6",
			distractor4: "IDIC",
			correctAnswer: "Servo",
			questionPic: "servo",
			questionPicAlt: "Gary Seven holding a servo"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 23,
			question: "Who was the one member of the Platonians who did not have their psychokenetic powers?",
			distractor1: "Parmen",
			distractor2: "Eraclitus",
			distractor3: "Alexander",
			distractor4: "Philana",
			correctAnswer: "Alexander",
			questionPic: "alex",
			questionPicAlt: "Alexander and Kirk in 'Plato's Stepchildren'"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 24,
			question: "What actor &mdash; best known for playing the Riddler in the 1960s <em>Batman</em> television series &mdash; played the black-and-white-skinned alien Bele?",
			distractor1: "Frank Gorshin",
			distractor2: "John Astin",
			distractor3: "Burgess Meredith",
			distractor4: "Cesar Romero",
			correctAnswer: "Frank Gorshin",
			questionPic: "bele",
			questionPicAlt: "Bele"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 25,
			question: "In <em>The Way to Eden</em>, what slang name for bureaucratic officials did Dr. Sevrin's followers continually call Captain Kirk?",
			distractor1: "Ralph",
			distractor2: "Fred",
			distractor3: "Basil",
			distractor4: "Herbert",
			correctAnswer: "Herbert",
			questionPic: "eden",
			questionPicAlt: "Adam from 'The Way to Eden'"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 26,
			question: "Who was the founder of the Klingon Empire?",
			distractor1: "Kang",
			distractor2: "Kor",
			distractor3: "Korax",
			distractor4: "Kahless",
			correctAnswer: "Kahless",
			questionPic: "kahless",
			questionPicAlt: "Kahless the Unforgettable"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 27,
			question: "What is Captain Kirk's middle name?",
			distractor1: "Thomas",
			distractor2: "Romulus",
			distractor3: "Tiberius",
			distractor4: "Augustus",
			correctAnswer: "Tiberius",
			questionPic: "kirkt",
			questionPicAlt: "James T. Kirk"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 28,
			question: "What planet is Spock's mother from?",
			distractor1: "Rigel",
			distractor2: "Earth",
			distractor3: "Beta III",
			distractor4: "Andoria",
			correctAnswer: "Earth",
			questionPic: "amanda",
			questionPicAlt: "Amanda and Spock"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 29,
			question: "What is the registry number of the <em>U.S.S. Enterprise</em>?",
			distractor1: "NCC-1657",
			distractor2: "NCC-1709",
			distractor3: "NCC-1701",
			distractor4: "NCC-176",
			correctAnswer: "NCC-1701",
			questionPic: "ncc",
			questionPicAlt: "The U.S.S. Enterprise"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 30,
			question: "What division do uniforms with blue tunics represent?",
			distractor1: "Operations",
			distractor2: "Command",
			distractor3: "Science",
			distractor4: "Recreation",
			correctAnswer: "Science",
			questionPic: "blues",
			questionPicAlt: "Starfleet blue uniform"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 31,
			question: "Actor Mark Lenard portrayed the first Romulan commander encountered by the <em>Enterprise</em> and later played which famous Vulcan?",
			distractor1: "Surak",
			distractor2: "Stonn",
			distractor3: "Sarek",
			distractor4: "Sybok",
			correctAnswer: "Sarek",
			questionPic: "sarek",
			questionPicAlt: "Sarek"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 32,
			question: "Who is the social worker Kirk fell in love with when he and Spock were stranded in the 1940's?",
			distractor1: "Nancy Hedford",
			distractor2: "Janice Lester",
			distractor3: "Edith Keeler",
			distractor4: "Carolyn Palamas",
			correctAnswer: "Edith Keeler",
			questionPic: "keeler",
			questionPicAlt: "Edith Keeler"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 33,
			question: "What is the name of the bully from Kirk's Starfleet Academy days who like to play practical jokes on him?",
			distractor1: "Gary Mitchell",
			distractor2: "Ben Finney",
			distractor3: "Finnegan",
			distractor4: "Tyree",
			correctAnswer: "Finnegan",
			questionPic: "finn",
			questionPicAlt: "Kirk's bully"
		},
		objQuestion = {
			id: 34,
			question: "Which character is a Shakespearean actor who Captain Kirk suspected was the mass murderer  <em>Kodos the Executioner</em>?",
			distractor1: "Thomas Leighton",
			distractor2: "Kevin Riley",
			distractor3: "Anton Karidian",
			distractor4: "Patrick Stewart",
			correctAnswer: "Anton Karidian",
			questionPic: "king",
			questionPicAlt: "Kodos the Executioner"
		}
	]
